hello everyone this is Rahul zakara from
sherka welcome back to exciting 3
actionable stock updates 3 basically
means right sector right quality and
right valuation these are our investment
ideas today we have an update on ICI
lomard our analyst maintains buy rating
on IC Lombard with a price target of
rupees
2550 the competitive environment has
relatively become favorable leading to
healthy underlying business Trends
providing Tailwinds to growth and
profitability we expect the company to
deliver Roe of 18 to 20% in near to
medium ter at the current market price
the stock trades at 33.6 times at SEI 26
and 28.2 times at SEI 27 EPS estimate
the stock is outperformed the broader
indices in last 12 months next we have
an update on infosis
limited our maintains Buy on infosis
with a price target of rupes 250 as the
company is seeing early signs of
improvement in financial services in US
particularly in mortgages Capital
markets and card payments the company
has raised Revenue growth guidance for
fi25 on the back of strong performance
in quarter 1 and Financial Service deals
in North America we expect 7% sales and
12% pad cagr over f24 to f26 at the
current market price the stock trades at
28. 1 times at F525 and 23.6 times at FY
26 estimated
EPS investment and securities Market are
subject to Market risks read all the
related documents carefully before
investing